if you continue to meet roadblocks in the system that you're in, nothing says that you just can't
build your own shit. And here's what we're going to do. We're actually going to connect you to
people that can support you in doing that. We're going to help build your skills around how to
write a business plan and a financial model. Foundational stuff. Exactly. Because so many
of us, like so many of our brilliant ideas die on the vine. Not because we're not entrepreneurs,
like our whole community and existence has been built on hustle culture. The candy lady in the
neighborhood, the ice cream. Maybe that was just my neighborhood. But you know, that's who we are and
who we have been. But recognizing that to bring these things to scale, we need to invest in our
people. We need to see their ideas as promising. And those of us who are in a position where we might
have access to a little bit of power, a little bit of money, whatever, leverage it to support them.